- 嘿, 唐纳.
- 嗨.
- Hey, Donna.
- Hi.
- 詹姆斯, 进来吧.
- 嗨.
- James, come on in.
- Hi.
我们正想来跟
马蒂道别.
We just came
to say goodbye to Maddy.
哦, 不好意思, 你刚错过了.
Oh, I'm sorry, you just missed her.
其实, 我刚在车站
放下她还不到20分钟呢.
In fact, I dropped her off
at the bus station not 20 minutes ago.
- 她已经走了?
- 是的.
- She's gone?
- Yes.
她已为你们
昨晚回来呢.
She thought that you were coming
over Iast night.
她说什么了没有?
Did she say anything?
嗯, 我只能说
她有一点点失望.
WeII, I wouId have to say that
she was a IittIe bit disappointed.
利兰?
LeIand?
利兰, 亲爱的?
LeIand, honey?
失陪了一会儿.
Excuse me.
知道吗, 如果你们愿意,
可以写信给她.
You know, if you'd Iike,
you couId write her.
我保证她一定会很高兴
收到你们的消息.
I'm sure she'd be gIad
to hear from you.
对. 看, 真不好意思
我们来打搅你了.
Yeah. Look, I'm sorry
we bothered you.
嘿, 没那回事儿, 没那回事儿.
Hey, no bother, no bother.
- 替我问候你家人, 唐娜.
- 好的.
- Say hi to your foIks for me, Donna.
- Okay.
- 好了.
- 再见, 帕尔默先生.
- Okay.
- Goodbye, Mr. PaImer.
再见, 詹姆斯.
Bye, James.
- 慢走了.
- 好的.
- Take it easy now.
- AII right.
- 利兰?
- 是, 亲爱的.
- LeIand?
- Yes, dear.
记得我们要在俱乐部登记
『格伦米勒夜』晚会.
Remember to sign us up for
the GIenn MiIIer Night at the cIub.
别担心, 亲爱的, 我不会忘的.
Don't worry, dear, I won't forget.
- 走了, 甜心.
- 再见, 利兰.
- Bye, hon.
- Bye, LeIand.
这里臭的像厕所.
难道就不能...
It smeIIs Iike a toiIet in here.
There's nothing...
杰利, 你搞什么鬼
这么久才来?
Jerry, what the heII
took you so Iong?
啊呀, 日界线, 时区,
我都搞不清我到底在哪儿了.
Gee, dateIines, time zones,
I don't even know where I am.
上帝啊, 你的样子好吓人.
God, you Iook terribIe.
- 杰利.
- 本.
- Jerry.
- Ben.
来, 本,
既然你自己的律师代表
WeII, Ben,
since your reguIar mouthpiece
也自身难保
被控谋杀,
has been charged
with murder himseIf,
我打算亲自处理你的案子
那我们开始吧.
I'm gonna be handIing your case
personaIIy. So Iet's get started.
你有杀她吗?
Did you kiII her?
- 杰利, 看在上帝的份上,.
- 对不起, 你是对的.
- Jerry, for God's sakes.
- Sorry, you're right.
真相是一个好辩护律师
必须要知道的.
The Iast thing a good defense attorney
needs to know is the truth.
杰利, 你能把我弄出去吗?
Jerry, can you get me out of here?
嗯, 再找不到具体的指控罪名
他们最多只能扣留你24小时.
WeII, they can onIy hoId you
for 24 hours without charging you.
还是48小时?
Or is it 48?
噢, 杰利, 杰利,
我现在出事了.
Oh, Jerry, Jerry,
I am in troubIe here.
自控, 哥哥.
Under controI, big brother.
好了, 我们刚讲到
劳拉死的那晚，你在哪儿?
Okay, so where are we saying
you were on the night Laura died?
- 我和凯萨琳在一起.
- 那可不是个好选择.
- I was with Catherine.
- That's not a good choice.
但恰恰是这样.
It happens to be the truth.
哦, 亲爱的人.
Oh, dear.
还有任何她的东西留下吗?
比如-- 骨头碎片或牙齿之类的?
Is there any sign of her?
Bone-- Bone fragments or teeth?
那本烧焦的证据账本
有提到你关于你下落吗?
Charred corroborating note
regarding your whereabouts?
我好沮丧啊.
I'm so depressed.
双层床.
Bunk beds.
你还记得
我们的第一间房吗, 本?
Do you remember
our first room, Ben?
我在上层
而你在下层.
Me on the top bunk
and you on the bottom bunk.
路易丝·当博斯奇拿着手电筒
在编织地毯上跳舞.
And Louise Dombrowski dancing
on the hook rug with a fIashIight.
神啊, 是什么造就了我们?
Lord, what's become of us?
你知道吗, 我第一次去时,
You know, the first time I went in,
他们还以为那是膀胱,
所以他们又检查了一次.
they thought it was my bIadder,
so they checked it again.
其实是感染.
我还从没接近过锈钉.
It was an infection.
I hadn't even been near a rusty naiI.
我是说, 你还记得那次
我的脚趾发紫, 对吗?
I mean, you remember that time
my toe turned purpIe, right?
作为替代, 我用烤过的苏打水
洗了个澡，然后我的脚趾就好了,
So instead, I took a bath in baking
soda and then my toe came around,
但我还得过最严重的抽筋
but I got the worst cramps
就像把扭成一团的
水管吞进肚子里似的.
Iike I swaIIowed
a kinked hose or something.
你见过安迪?
Have you seen Andy?
噢, 你肯定是那个印第安人
我听说过你好多事, 叫鹰眼?
Oh, you must be that native person
I've heard so much about, EagIe Eye?
叫豪克. 你姐姐?
Hawk. Sister?
哦, 对, 这是我姐关.
这是豪克.
Oh, yeah, this is my sister Gwen.
This is Hawk.
噢, 真高兴见到你.
Oh, it's a pIeasure to meet you.
天啊, 你肯定很憎恨我们白人
毕竟我们对你们做过那么多的坏事.
God, how you must hate us white
peopIe after aII we've done to you.
我一些最好的朋友
也是白人.
Some of my best friends
are white peopIe.
总之, 噢, 乖乖.
我的胃...
Anyway, oh, come on.
My stomach...
戴安, 上午10:03,
北方大酒店.
Diane, 1 0:03 a.m.,
Great Northern HoteI.
杜鲁门警长和我
刚和独臂人一起,
Sheriff Truman and I have just been
with the one-armed man,
刚从他房里出来.
or what's Ieft of him.
在另一个时间, 另一种文化,
In another time, another cuIture,
他或许早就是个
先知, 或者是萨满教巫师.
he may have been
a seer, a shaman priest.
而在我们的世界, 他只是个
生活在阴暗中的鞋贩子.
In our worId, he's a shoe saIesman
and Iives among the shadows.
利兰·帕尔默.
LeIand PaImer.
不好意思.
Excuse me.
他知道
我们拘捕了本·荷恩?
Does he know
we arrested Ben Horne?
看起来不像知道.
Doesn't Iook Iike it.
哈里, 你最好亲自告诉他.
Harry, best if he'd hear it from you.
嗨, 哈里, 库珀探员.
刚巧在这儿玩一下.
Hi, Harry, Agent Cooper.
Just having a IittIe fun.
你气色不错, 利兰.
You're Iooking good, LeIand.
叫我佛瑞德好了.
Just caII me Fred.
利兰, 我很遗憾.
LeIand, I'm sorry.
但我们不希望你是从
别人哪儿得到这消息的.
We didn't want you
to hear it from anyone eIse.
我们已经拘捕了本·荷恩
怀疑他谋杀了劳拉.
We've arrested Ben Horne
for Laura's murder.
他还没被起诉,
但我们拘留他了.
He hasn't been charged,
but we're hoIding him.
- 本?
- 是的.
- Ben?
- That's right.
那肯定是个
误会, 哈里.
There must be
some mistake, Harry.
本?
Ben?
- 我以为是雅克·雷诺干的--
- 不.
- I thought that Jacques RenauIt had--
- No.
本.
Ben.
- 你们有有利的形势对付他吗?
- 是的, 我们有.
- You have a strong case against him?
- Yes, we do.
噢, 天啊.
Oh, God.
你没事吧, 利兰?
WiII you be aII right, LeIand?
是啊.
Yeah.
- 留给法律去处理这事吧.
- 正是如此.
- The Iaw wiII handIe this.
- As it shouId be.
谢谢, 哈里. 库珀探员.
Thanks, Harry. Agent Cooper.
哈里, 我等一下再去找你.
Harry, I'II catch up with you.
利兰?
LeIand?
是.
Yes.
如果你记得劳拉死的那晚
荷恩先生有任何的
If you can remember anything unusuaI
about Mr. Horne's behavior
异常行为,
请你及时告诉我?
the night of Laura's death,
wouId you pIease Iet me know?
我会的, 当然.
I wiII, of course.
谢谢你.
Thank you.
还好吧?
Everything okay?
我不肯定.
I'm not sure.
这个一点儿都不疼.
This won't hurt a bit.
警长, 我抗议这么野蛮的对待
我的委托人.
Sheriff, I protest this brutaI treatment
of my cIient.
毕竟这个人
为这个镇做过许多...
After aII this man
has done for this town...
现在, 保持冷静.
Now, hoId stiII.
2小时后
就会有结果了.
I'II have the resuIts
in a coupIe of hours.
- 谢了, 医生.
- 先生们,
- Thanks, doc.
- GentIemen,
我请求要不起诉我的当事人
就释放他.
I demand that my cIient
either be reIeased or charged.
我执业生涯里
从没见过如此
Never in aII my years of practicing Iaw
have I witnessed such a compIete
完全绝对忽视
被告权利的.
and utter disregard for
an accused man's constitutionaI rights.
杰利米·荷恩,
宫扎格大学, 1974.
Jeremy Horne,
Gonzaga University, 1 97 4.
班上142人，毕业最后一名.
Graduated Iast in his cIass of 1 42.
3次才通过律师行会审核.
Passed the bar on his third attempt.
后来执业执照
被吊销
License to practice
revoked in the states
包括在本国的伊利诺斯州, 佛罗里达州,
阿拉斯加州, 马萨诸塞州.
of IIIinois, FIorida,
AIaska, Massachusetts.
嘿, 我可不是来这儿受审的.
Hey, I'm not on triaI here.
坐下.
Sit down.
荷恩先生, 你知道这是什么吗
Mr. Horne, do you know what this is?
- 一本书.
- A book.
拿近点看.
Take a cIoser Iook.
一本日记.
A diary.
单眼杰克的事我们全都知道了.
We aII know about One-Eyed Jack's.
劳拉也知道.
So did Laura.
"有朝一日, 我要把本·荷恩
公之于众.
''Someday, I'm gonna teII the worId
aII about Ben Horne.
我要让大家知道真正的本·荷恩."
I'm gonna teII them who he reaIIy is.''
但她永远没机会了, 不是吗?
She never got the chance, did she?
来吧, 本, 我们这儿都是成年人了.
Come on, Ben, we're aII aduIts here.
像劳拉·帕尔默这样年轻又野的女孩,
事态失控了.
WiId, young girI Iike Laura PaImer,
things spin out of controI.
她不单威胁到你个人,
还有你的事业, 和家庭.
She becomes a threat not just to you,
but to your business, your famiIy.
你太嚣张了.
You are way out of Iine.
好, 也许
你没什么需要隐藏的.
WeII, maybe
you don't have anything to hide.
但这里可不是这样说的.
That's not what it says in here.
- 你不能用这种方式和我讲话!
- 本. 本.
- You cannot taIk to me Iike this!
- Ben. Ben.
- 你不能, 你懂吗?
- 坐下.
- You cannot, you understand?
- Sit down.
别激动. 先生们, 我想
和我哥哥单独呆会儿--
Nice and easy. GentIemen, I'd Iike
a moment aIone with my brother--
也是我的委托人.
With my cIient.
如果你们不介意?
If you don't mind?
你们自便吧.
You have your moment.
本, 本.
Ben, Ben.
本, 如果你就那样
冲口而出招供了,
Ben, if you're gonna bIurt out
a confession Iike that,
那会让我们
一点回转的余地都没有了.
it's gonna make our options
shrink down to a tiny IittIe nub.
那好, 我们现在怎么办?
我们现在该怎么办?
AII right, what are we gonna do?
What are we gonna do?
你的不在场证据已经被烤焦了.
Your aIibi has been roasted.
他们就能捏造一个动机.
They can estabIish motive.
还有你的血
也许有劳拉的指纹在上面.
And your bIood
may have Laura's fingerprints on it.
本, 作为你的律师,
Ben, as your attorney,
你的朋友, 和弟弟,
your friend, and your brother,
我强烈建议
你要给自己找个更好的律师.
I strongIy suggest
that you get yourseIf a better Iawyer.
好, 最后一次机会, 里欧.
别让我失望.
Okay, one last chance, Leo.
Don't disappoint me.
锯木厂吗?
The mill?
好, 最后一次机会, 里欧.
别让我失望.
Okay, one last chance, Leo.
Don't disappoint me.
锯木厂吗?
The mill?
简单来说.
Keep it simple.
保险调查员
因该会察觉到是 "纵火. "
lnsurance investigators
should read ''arson. ''
用正楷体约有6英尺高.
Block letters about 6 feet high.
就像我们之前商量好的?
The deal as we discussed?
本·荷恩, 是他的声音,
Ben Horne, his voice,
还有强生的声音, 本和里欧.
and Johnson's voice, Ben and Leo.
荷恩先生的特别快递来了.
SpeciaI deIivery for Mr. Horne.
波比. 噢, 天啊. 波比!
Bobby. Oh, God. Bobby!
他又来了.
He did it again.
这次轮到你去清洁他了.
It's your turn to cIean him this time.
那是什么?
What's that?
我们的船票.
That is our ship.
什么意思?
What's that mean?
自从隔壁房的那颗摇钱树
已经阴沟里翻了船,
Since our cash cow in the other room
has turned into a sinkhoIe,
我决定在商业领域
追逐事业了.
I've decided to pursue a career
in business.
真的? 像推销员?
ReaIIy? Like a saIesman?
哦, 才不, 我在想
领导层更适合我.
Oh, no, I'm thinking
more executive suite.
- 真的吗?
- 当然.
- ReaIIy?
- Yeah.
波比, 那太好了.
Bobby, that sounds great.
我会给你
任何你想要的.
I'm gonna give you
anything you want.
我想要个全职保姆.
I want a fuII-time nanny.
- 法国女仆怎样.
- 波比.
- Maybe a French maid.
- Bobby.
- 你好, 诺玛.
- 妈妈.
- HeIIo, Norma.
- Mother.
我相信那是真土豆做的
而不是薯粉?
I trust those are reaI potatoes
and not fIakes?
真土豆
ReaI potatoes.
打搅了.
Excuse me.
真惊喜见到你在这儿.
What a nice surprise to see you here.
嘿, 那个味道不错.
Hey, those are good.
我看见他们
在围栏里教他技巧.
I see they taught
him a skiII in the stockade.
- 你的万人迷丈夫呢?
- 汉克? 他现在不在.
- Where is your charming husband?
- Hank? He's not here right now.
知道.
I see.
妈妈, 我收到你的信了.
但如果你不介意,
Mother, I got your message.
But if you don't mind my asking,
我想知道,你到这来干嘛?
what are you doing here?
我想向你介绍
我的新丈夫.
I want to introduce you
to my new husband.
丈夫?
Husband?
尔尼, 这是诺玛.
Ernie, this is Norma.
嗨, 你好吗?
Hi, how are you?
我们正在度蜜月呢.
We're honeymooning.
我能否
麻烦你来杯咖啡呢?
I wonder if I couId
bother you for a cup of coffee?
- 好女孩.
- 她可是个宝贝.
- Nice girI.
- She's darIing.
尔尼是个金融分析师.
Ernie's a financiaI anaIyst.
我爱喜欢你
布置的餐厅了, 亲爱的.
I just Iove what you've done
with your diner, darIing.
那些花放的恰到好处
让人愉悦.
The fIowers add
such a measure of cheer.
哦, 谢谢你. 太谢谢你了.
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much.
真高兴看到你的美貌
毫无保留的遗传了给下一代.
Nice to see those good Iooks haven't
isoIated themseIves to one generation.
- 是, 我知道, 金价现在多少.
- 失陪了.
- Yeah, I know, go with goId figures.
- Excuse me.
你穿制服
看起来还是那么醒目.
You stiII Iook very smart
in that uniform.
样子还是那么可爱.
一点儿都没变过.
Your figure's IoveIy.
It hasn't changed.
既然这样, 恕我无礼,
那你打算要在这儿呆多久?
Now, I don't mean to be rude,
but how Iong wiII you be staying?
2天吧. 尔尼想
在乡村到处走走看看.
A coupIe of days. Ernie wanted
to see something of the country.
为什么这样问?
Why?
我也想知道为什么, 没事了.
I just wish I had known, that's aII.
哦, 我不想你
为此大惊小怪.
Oh, I didn't mean for you
to go into any fuss.
你是知道我的, 亲爱的, 我很从容.
You know me, dear, I'm easy.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
没什么, 只是有个
食评家要来了
Nothing, it's just that
there's a food critic coming
我人手不够, 就那样而已.
and I'm short on heIp, that's aII.
食评家.
Food critic.
怪不得你把地方
布置的这么漂亮.
So that's why you tried so hard
to make the pIace Iook nice.
诺玛, 希望有时间
多和你聊聊.
Norma, hoping to spend
much more time with you.
差不多了吧, 我们先去酒店吧.
If it's aII right, we'd better check in.
我要接个
东京来的传真.
I've got a Tokyo fax
waiting for me at the desk.
我们在大北房.
We'II be at the Great Northern.
真遗憾没见到小汉克.
等一下给你电话, 好吗?
I'm sorry we missed Henry.
I'II caII you Iater, okay?
好. 很高兴见到你.
Okay. Nice to meet you.
他在附近.
He's cIose.
护士.
Nurse.
能请你给我
一杯水吗?
CouId I have
a gIass of water, pIease?
好的, 先生.
Yes, sir.
对不起.
I'm sorry.
嗨, 诺玛.
Hi, Norma.
我想我迟到了.
I guess I'm a IittIe Iate.
48小时不是迟到, 汉克,
是失踪.
Forty-eight hours is not Iate, Hank,
it's missing.
对不起, 因为有点--
有点公事我不得不去处理.
I'm sorry, it was some--
Some business I had to take care of.
有点公事? 不, 这才是公事.
Business? No, this is business.
公事就是无论你喜欢与否
都必须要去的一个地方.
Business is a pIace where you come to
whether you feeI Iike it or not.
- 诺玛, 我--
- 别对我甜言蜜语了,
- Norma, I--
- Don't sweet-taIk me,
我告诉你
离我远点说话.
I'm this far from teIIing you
to take a hike.
诺玛, 在我解释前
请你不要妄下判断.
Norma, pIease don't make that
kind of judgment untiI you hear me out.
因为我之前一些
错误的选择,
Because of the bad choices
I've made,
有些正冷眼旁观的人,
there are peopIe out there,
那些知道我过去的人
都等着看我笑话呢.
peopIe from my past
who wanna see me faiI.
我尝试着对付他们,
没想到却惹来更多麻烦.
I've tried fighting them,
but I just get in more troubIe.
我试着逃离他们,
但追我的人总比我快一步.
I've tried running from them,
but there's aIways somebody faster.
我知道一个人不能
老这样过活,
I know it's no way for a man
to Iive his Iife,
但有时候最好的方法
but sometimes it's just best
还是坚持着等待
暴风雨过去.
to hoId up and wait
for the storm to pass.
我没有伤害你的意思.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
我仅仅是为了
挣扎求存.
I'm just trying to keep my head
above water.
希望下次,
你会要求别人的帮助.
Maybe next time,
you'II ask for a IittIe heIp.
下次, 我会的.
Next time, I wiII.
哇, 浪子回头啦.
WeII, the prodigaI son returns.
- 维维安.
- 嗨.
- Vivian.
- Hi.
- 你气色真好.
- 谢谢.
- You Iook great.
- Thanks.
你在监狱还好吧?
Prison treat you weII?
嗯, 说来话长.
WeII, that's a Iong story.
那今晚一起晚餐时讲给我听吧.
见见我的新丈夫.
I'd Iike to hear it over dinner tonight.
I have a new husband.
- 大北方, 8:30?
- 我们乐意之极.
- Great Northern, 8:30?
- We'd Iove to.
- 我想我不能去了.
- 没事,去吧, 甜心.
- I don't think if I'II be abIe to get there.
- We'II be fine, honey.
8:30正, 我们会到的.
Eight-thirty sharp, we'II be there.
- 哈里?
- 哦, 你好, 皮特.
- Harry?
- Oh, heIIo, Pete.
在看啥呢?
What you got?
啄木鸟.
Woodpecker.
我看是红冠黑.
PiIeated, I think.
是啊. 你看.
Yeah. Here.
红冠黑啄木鸟.
PiIeated woodpecker.
太出色了.
Outstanding.
哈里?
Harry?
说吧, 皮特.
Yeah, Pete.
哈里, 乔西走了.
Harry, Josie's gone.
是啊, 我知道.
Yeah, I know.
当我下晚班
回到家,
When I came home
from the Iate shift,
她留个条子在厨房的桌子上,
没有解释, 没有再见.
she Ieft a note on the kitchen tabIe,
no expIanations, no goodbyes.
就一张纸条.
A note.
她把锯木厂卖了给本·荷恩.
She soId the miII to Ben Horne.
嗯, 不完全是.
WeII, not exactIy.
你不必解释了.
You don't have to expIain.
我爱她.
I Ioved her.
瞧. 我说出来了.
There. I said it.
别见怪, 哈里.
No offense, Harry.
我也爱她.
I Ioved her too.
我站在那儿亲眼看着她走.
还有她的助手
I stood there and watched her go.
Watched her assistant
拿着她的行李离开了.
carry her bags away.
她的助手?
Her assistant?
是啊, 亚洲人.
以前从没见过他.
Yeah, Asian feIIow.
Never saw him before.
他长什么样?
What did he Iook Iike?
一般高,
中等身材, 马尾辫子.
Average height,
medium buiId, ponytaiI.
噢, 那是他表哥, 叫乔纳森.
Oh, that was her cousin, Jonathan.
她说那是她助手,
李先生.
She said it was her assistant,
Mr. Lee.
李先生?
Mr. Lee?
哈里, 我有不祥感.
Harry, I have a bad feeIing.
- 我也有同感, 皮特.
- 哈里.
- I'm right there with you, Pete.
- Harry.
你好, 皮特. 杰勒德不见了.
他把警卫打昏了.
HeIIo, Pete. Gerard's missing.
He knocked the deputy out.
皮特, 抱歉我们得走了.
Pete, you'II have to excuse us.
他跑不远的.
He don't get far.
嗨, 警长. 库珀探员.
Hi, sheriff. Agent Cooper.
露西?
Lucy?
- 露西?
- 怎么了?
- Lucy?
- What?
安迪?
Andy?
幸灾乐祸吧, 皮特.
Step right in, Pete.
我们这些绝望罪犯
被安全的关在自己的笼子里了.
We desperate criminaIs
are Iocked safeIy in our cages.
我有个口信给你.
I have a message for you.
锯木厂那些小伙子们
的问候?
Greetings from the boys
down at the miII?
但先来点音乐.
But first, a IittIe music.
你好, 本杰明.
Hello, Benjamin.
噢, 很抱歉我没有
亲自去探望你, 亲爱的.
Oh, l'm sorry l haven't
dropped by for a visit, dear.
因为我非常厌恶
去监狱.
But l have a strong aversion
to prisons.
- 那里太恶心了--
- 她还活着?
- How awful--
- She's aIive?
我们共度的那晚
迷失在爱意里.
The night we spent together
lost in love.
那时什么时候的事了?
似乎那么的遥远.
When was that?
lt seems so long ago.
就像做了一个梦.
Almost like a dream.
噢, 对, 我记起来了,
就是劳拉·帕尔默死的那晚.
Oh, yes, l remember,
it was the night Laura Palmer died.
记忆最终是不可靠的,
那也许只是个梦.
Memory is so unreliable finally,
maybe it was a dream.
也许从未发生过.
Maybe it never happened.
告诉你吧,
我再也不能确定了.
To tell you the truth,
l can't be sure anymore.
她想要什么? 我什么都给.
她想要什么?
What does she want? I'II pay anything.
What does she want?
你还好吧, 笨笨?
You okay there, Benji?
想交换我的证言, 亲爱的,
ln exchange for my testimony, dear,
你要把锯木厂
和格斯伍的地产合同签回来给我.
you will sign the mill and
Ghostwood Estates back over to me.
我会考虑把你的宝贝酒店
租给你用.
l will consider letting you keep
your precious hotel.
我的代理人
在24小时内
A representative of mine
will come to you
会带上文件去见你.
with the documents within 2 4 hours.
如果你不合作...
lf you won't cooperate...
那好, 我相信
你放出去以后
Well, l'm confident
that you'll go on from here
由联邦监狱系统
提供的众多工作机会里
to excel in one or another
of the many fine career opportunities
其中一定有一个
是你能够胜任的.
offered by the federal
prison system.
本, 再见到你真好.
Ben, so nice to see you again.
她设计陷害我.
She set me up.
那个凯萨琳.
That Catherine.
她陷害我.
She set me up.
她可是个危险人物, 不是吗?
She's a cautioned, isn't she?
你陷害我!
你这婊子! 你这婊子!
You set me up!
You bitch! You bitch!
我不会放过你的, 你这婊子.
I'II get you, you bitch.
想害我.
Set me up.
小鸡小鸭小鹅鹅
赶快散开
Chicks and ducks and geese
Better scurry
当我带着你乘马车外出
When l take you out in the surrey
车顶装饰着漂亮的流苏
With the fringe on top
当我带着你乘马车外出
When l take you out in the surrey
车顶装饰着漂亮的流苏
With the fringe on top
哈里, 驾驶课程在你们学校里
是强制学习的吗?
Harry, are driver education programs
mandatory in your schooI system?
是的.
Yep.
我想我们逮到一个退学生了.
哈里, 小心.
I think we got a dropout.
Harry, Iook out.
车顶装饰着漂亮的流苏
With the fringe on top
利兰.
LeIand.
库珀探员, 哈里, 对不起.
Agent Cooper, Harry, I'm sorry.
- 你们2个没事吧?
- 利兰, 我们没事. 你呢?
- Are you two aII right?
- LeIand, we're fine. How about you?
噢, 当然, 我还好, 我还好.
Oh, sure, I'm fine, I'm fine.
正准备去俱乐部
试试一套新的铁杆,
I was just on my way to the cIub
to try out a new set of irons,
而且要开始仔细
想想有关本的事了.
and I must have started
thinking about Ben.
我想我糊涂了.
I guess my mind just wandered.
开车时别开小差
是个好主意.
It's a good idea to Ieave your troubIes
at home when operating a vehicIe.
你是对的, 理所当然.
我道歉.
You're right, of course.
My apoIogies.
我的确记起些事来, 就你之前问
有关劳拉死的那晚.
I did remember something, as
you asked, about the night Laura died.
本和我在办公室工作到很晚
那时大约是10点左右.
I was working Iate at the office
with Ben, it was about 1 0:00.
他离开办公室
去打了一个电话.
He Ieft the room
to make a phone caII.
我不知道他和谁在讲电话,
但他声音很高, 他当时很生气.
I don't know who he was taIking to, but
his voice was raised, he was angry.
我听见他提到了
什么
I heard him mention
something about
一本日记.
a dairy.
- 一本日记?
- 我想是的, 对.
- A dairy?
- That's what I think, yes.
- 一本日记.
- 有可能是.
- A diary.
- That couId be it.
杜鲁门警长, 杜鲁门警长,
我是露西.
Sheriff Truman, Sheriff Truman,
this is Lucy.
请回话, 警长?
豪克有紧急消息.
Are you there, sheriff?
l have an urgent message from Hawk.
- 你打高尔夫吗, 库珀探员?
- 打, 利兰, 我喜欢它对精确度的要求.
- Do you pIay goIf, Agent Cooper?
- Yes, LeIand, I enjoy its precision.
什么时候,我想邀请你
到俱乐部去打一局.
I'd Iike to invite you for a round
at the cIub someday.
来看看我的新球杆?
May I show you my new cIubs?
好吧.
Sure.
库珀.
Cooper.
他们在瀑布旁
发现杰勒德了.
They found Gerard.
Near the waterfaII.
赶快过去. 他们正等着我们呢.
Better go. They're waiting for us.
我们去接他. 利兰,
我们改天再看球杆吧.
Let's go get him. LeIand,
we'II see those cIubs another time.
我明白, 库珀探员.
如果有什么能帮的上忙的
I understand, Agent Cooper.
You Iet me know
- 一定告诉我.
- 会的.
- if there's anything I can do to heIp.
- WiII do.
可怜的安迪.
Poor Andy.
知道吗, 在我身上确实发生过
同样的事
You know, the exact same thing
happened to me
当我第一次怀孕时.
when I first got pregnant.
我会外出购物,
I wouId be out shopping,
然后砰一下, 就在卖农产品货架那儿
晕倒了.
and then boom, pass right out
in the produce section.
紧接下来就是浑身的瘀伤
还有那些被压烂的水果,
Then come to covered in bruises
and crushed fruit,
那些陌生人都站一旁围着我
等着看我是不是死了.
and strangers standing over me
waiting to see if I was dead.
你看, 人啊就想把快乐
建筑在别人的痛苦上, 我懂.
You see, peopIe want terribIe things
to happen to you, I know.
我想和你谈谈
关于我的精子.
I wanna taIk to you
about my sperms.
精子?
你知道吗, 那是每个男人都关心的.
Sperms?
You know, that is aII men think about.
你知道吗, 我记得
小卡尔刚出生时
You know, I remember
when IittIe CarI was first born
他们把他放在我怀里,
and they Iaid him out on my breast,
我低头看着
这个我生出来的小生物.
I Iooked down and saw what kind of
a tiny IittIe creature I was deaIing with.
然后我自己想, 我想,
"我的天啊, 正是世人所需要的,
And I thought to myseIf, I thought,
''My God, just what the worId needs,
又一支精子枪擦枪走火了. 对吧?
然后大喊一声,嘿,女人们小心了,我来了."
another sperm gun running around
Ioose. Right? Women beware.''
嗯, 我说真的.
WeII, I did.
我的做了2次测试.
第一次, 它们全死了.
I had mine counted twice.
The first time, they were aII dead.
噢, 伙计, 我每听一次
就笑一次.
Oh, man, if I had a nickeI
every time I heard that one.
- 第二次, 它们活蹦乱跳就像--
- 什么? 什么?
- Second time, they were jumping Iike--
- What? What?
--就像三文鱼逆流回潮.
--Iike saImon swimming upstream.
那个, 肯定了,
你满脑子回游产卵啊.
So, of course,
aII you couId think of was spawning.
- 闭嘴.
- 闭嘴, 关.
- Shut up.
- Shut up, Gwen.
所以当你告诉我怀孕时
我没有想到会是我的
So when you toId me that you were
pregnant, I didn't think it couId be me
因为按推测
我的精子那时是全死的.
because mine were aII dead
supposedIy at the time.
但它们好起来了.
通知我的消息搞错了. 我才是爸爸.
But they got better.
I was misinformed. I'm the father.
噢, 好家伙.
Oh, brother.
难道不是我吗?
Aren't I?
噢, 啊. 哦, 来这儿.
Oh, yeah. Oh, come here.
你想见你那个
小气的露西姑姑吗.
You want to see
your mean Aunt Lucy.
噢, 你不乖吗,
你这个小臭屁鬼.
Oh, aren't you neat,
you IittIe snooky-bookems.
他已经在附近了.
He's been cIose.
鲍勃现在不在这儿.
Bob is not here now.
警长. 警长?
Sheriff. Sheriff?
难道你就没有什么
要和我们解释的吗?
Isn't there something
that you'd Iike to share with us?
哦, 好极了.
Oh, great.
那请叫这人别再盯着狗饼干一样
盯着我了.
And wouId you teII this guy to stop
staring at me Iike I'm a dog biscuit.
鲍勃已经非常接近了.
Bob has been very cIose.
谁是鲍勃? 我不认识鲍勃.
Who's Bob? I don't know a Bob.
我们认识鲍勃吗?
Do we know a Bob?
警长, 我没恶意的, 但无疑,
这个人也不过是枉费心机罢了.
Sheriff, no offense, but cIearIy,
this man's stairs do not reach the attic.
现在, 你们的24小时已经结束了.
Now, your 24 hours are up.
你要不起诉我的当事人
要不马上放他走!
You either charge my cIient
or Iet him go!
本·荷恩, 我现在正式
起诉你谋杀劳拉·帕尔默.
Ben Horne, I'm charging you
with the murder of Laura PaImer.
啊. 英明决定, 杰.
Yeah. Good move, Jer.
豪克, 送杰勒德先生
回酒店l.
Hawk, take Mr. Gerard
back to the hoteI.
- 把所有窗户都钉牢了.
- 别. 别.
- NaiI aII the windows shut.
- No. No.
- 房间派2个警卫守着.
- 你这微不足道的伐木工.
- I want two men on the door.
- You two-bit Iumberjack.
- 你在这个镇上完蛋了.
- 别搞事了.
- You are finished in this town.
- Don't make it worse.
你彻底完蛋了.
You're finished.
- 冷静下来. 你想干什么?
- 出去一下, 好吗?
- CaIm down. What are you doing?
- Step outside, pIease?
我没事.
I'm aII right.
哈里. 哈里, 我们准备骑马前
要先给马上好鞍.
Harry. Harry, I think we're saddIing
the horse before we're ready to ride.
我不明白.
I don't foIIow.
我认为不是本·荷恩
杀的劳拉·帕尔默.
I don't think Ben Horne
kiIIed Laura PaImer.
- 什么?
- 你应该释放他.
- What?
- You shouId reIease him.
库珀?
Cooper?
每一步我都一直跟着你走.
但我真受够了那些什么催眠巫术.
I've backed you every step of the way.
I've had enough of the mumbo jumbo.
也受够了那些蛊惑人的什么梦,
什么幻象, 什么小侏儒, 还有什么巨人,
I've had enough of the dreams,
the visions, the dwarfs, the giants,
西藏和那些
骗人的灵魂出窍.
Tibet and the rest
of the hocus-pocus.
现在, 我们有铁证
对付本·荷恩.
Now, we've got hard evidence
against Ben Horne.
我的任务就是关起他.
It's my job to Iock him up.
你是对的, 哈里.
这是你的地盘.
You're right, Harry.
This is your back yard.
一个旁观者
有时也会把这点给忘了.
Sometimes an outsider
can forget that.
嗯, 三文鱼很新鲜,肉很结实
只是煮的有点过熟了.
WeII, the saImon was fresh and firm
and just a IittIe bit overdone.
- 我的也是.
- 我觉得刚好.
- Mine too.
- Just right.
失陪一会儿
可以吗?
WouId you excuse me
for a minute, pIease?
我和你一起去吧.
I'II join you.
女士们, 快去快回.
Ladies, hurry back.
你什么都不会说的,
对吧?
You're not gonna say anything,
are you?
如果维维安发现
我在里面呆过,她会--
If Vivian ever found out
I'd been inside she'd--
她会把我扔下公寓的.
She'd drop me fIat.
我喜欢你的新发色.
I Iike your new hair coIor.
尔尼·奈尔斯.
Ernie NiIes.
尔尼·奈尔斯教授.
Ernie ''The Professor'' NiIes.
- 那你是什么时候?
- 2周前.
- So when did you?
- A coupIe of weeks ago.
让我告诉你吧, 尔尼,
Let me teII you, Ernie,
没有你在的最后6个月里
那里简直糟透了.
without you in there to paI around with
the Iast six months were sheer heII.
再也没人去图书馆.
Nobody to go to the Iibrary with.
也没人轧制
车牌了.
Nobody to stamp out
Iicense pIates with.
那么, 你钓这富婆
来这儿干嘛?
So, what's your angIe here
with Miss Moneybags?
不钓了.
No angIe.
少来了, 兄弟,
我们之间还有什么秘密.
Come on, buddy,
we don't have any secrets.
维维安可是在钱堆儿里打滚的人.
Vivian's roIIing in dough.
我是在共和党筹款会上
认识维维安的.
I met Vivian
at a RepubIican fundraiser.
我们结婚了.
We're married.
你肯定跟她讲了
什么大话, 漫天大谎.
You must have toId her
some taII taIe, a whopper.
我最近试着不讲大话了
除了真相外.
I'm trying very hard to teII nothing
but the truth these days.
是一种治疗.
It's therapeutic.
维维安想我着手操作
她所有的投资.
And Vivian wants me to handIe
aII her investments.
那么你的呢?
介绍她认识你的高利贷主吗?
What about yours?
Introduce her to your Ioan shark?
我戒了, 我戒了, 汉克.
我不再赌了.
I'm out of it, I'm out of it, Hank.
I don't gambIe anymore.
我去参加聚会. 还去教堂.
I go to meetings. I go to church too.
那么, 维维安发现你
拿了教会的野餐基金跑路了
So, what happens when
Vivian finds out that you ran off
- 会怎么样呢?
- 我从没在教堂偷过东西.
- with the congregation's picnic fund?
- I never stoIe from a church.
我有存款还有些贷款.
It was a savings and Ioan.
我生病了, 得了一种疾病.
后来还清了债务.
I was sick, it was an iIIness.
I paid my debt.
现在是新生活, 清白的-- 改头换面了.
It's a new Iife, a cIean-- CIean sIate.
- 那么她真的不知道咯?
- 不知道.
- So she reaIIy doesn't know?
- No.
那好, 尔尼, 这我倒感兴趣了.
WeII, Ernie, this is interesting to me.
因为家对我来说
是这世界上最重要的.
Because famiIy is the most
important thing in the worId to me.
一个人一定要准备着
不惜一切代价去保护它.
One must be prepared
to pay any price to protect it.
你能不同意吗?
Don't you agree?
哦, 是, 是. 我完全同意.
Oh, yeah, yeah. I compIeteIy agree.
我们回头再仔细聊, 尔尼.
We'II taIk more Iater, Ernie.
我喜欢
在花园里聊天,
I've aIways enjoyed
our taIks in the yard,
男人对男人, 囚犯对囚犯.
man-to-man, prisoner-to-prisoner.
- 我们回来了.
- 女士们.
- We're back.
- Ladies.
我们来举杯庆祝一下
I wouId Iike to propose a toast
祝新婚夫妇
幸福快乐.
to the newIyweds
and their happiness.
谢谢你, 小汉克.
太有风度了.
Thank you, Henry.
It's very generous.
祝尔尼和维维安,
To Ernie and Vivian,
祝他们的未来和事业
更加成功.
to much success in their future
and aII their future deaIings.
太动听了.
How sweet.
太动人了.
That's sweet.
戴安, 晚上11:05. 我在
北方大酒店的房间里.
Diane, it's 1 1 :05 p.m. I'm in my room
at the Great Northern HoteI.
今晚天上没有一颗星星.
There's not a star in the sky tonight.
本·荷恩在拘留所.
Ben Horne is in custody.
范围收窄了, 戴安.
The traiI narrows, Diane.
我离答案很近了,
I'm very cIose,
但最后几步总是
最黑暗最难的.
but the Iast few steps are aIways
the darkest and most difficuIt.
- 嗨.
- 欧蕊?
- Hi.
- Audrey?
- 我能进来来聊聊吗?
- 好的.
- Can I come in and taIk?
- AII right.
- 你就是那里中枪了?
- 是啊.
- Is that where you got shot?
- Yeah.
你逮捕他了吗?
Did you arrest him?
是的.
Yeah.
是他干的吗?
Did he do it?
那留给法庭去裁定吧.
That's for a court to decide.
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
我怎么
现在已经不重要了.
What I think
doesn't reaIIy matter right now.
你逮捕他
是因为我所说的吗?
Did you arrest him
because of what I said?
部分吧.
OnIy in part.
但有帮助?
But it heIped?
有.
Yeah.
我曾想要的所有
不过是希望他爱我.
AII I ever reaIIy wanted
was for him to Iove me.
我肯定他是爱你的.
I'm sure that he does.
他为我感到羞耻.
He's ashamed of me.
不, 他不是的.
No, he's not.
库珀探员,
Agent Cooper,
我在单眼杰克赌场时,
我从没有, 从没有被任何人--
when I was at One-Eyed Jack's,
I never, never Iet anyone--
欧蕊, 你什么
都不必说了.
Audrey, you don't have
to say anything.
但我想让你知道.
I want you to know.
我知道.
I know.
我要接电话了.
I have to get that.
好吧.
Okay.
我是库珀. 在哪儿?
Cooper here. Where?
多久之前的事?
How Iong ago?
- 我马上就到.
- 出什么事啦?
- I'm on my way.
- What's wrong?
我要你回自己房间
把门锁好.
I want you to go to your room
and Iock the door.
- 为什么?
- 别问了, 照我说的做.
- Why?
- No questions, do what I say.
那好吧.
AII right.
是马蒂·弗格逊.
It's Maddy Ferguson.